<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Breaking News Network</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Breaking News Network</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Breaking News Network (BNN), the only full-time, dedicated, incident notification system.&#xA;Our news-gathering capability depends on our professionally staffed 24 hours news desk as well as member participation.&#xA;Members include many public safety agencies and personnel, most major media outlets, news reporters and photographers, and commercial insurance professionals.&#xA;The BNN service is available to your mobile device using our iPhone and Android Applications, or by our optional desktop visual news client, Webview.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;customer-service&#34;&gt;Customer Service&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Customer service is available:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Monday 8:00a-5:00p &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Tuesday 8:00a-5:00p &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Wednesday 8:00a-5:00p &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Thursday 8:00a-5:00p &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Friday 8:00a-5:00p&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We can reached at 888-875-6100 during business hours or by &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:support@breakingnewsnetwork.com&#34;&gt;support@breakingnewsnetwork.com&lt;/a&gt; anytime.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/subscribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/subscribe/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incicents</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/incidents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/incidents/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;breaking-news---few-hours-ago&#34;&gt;Breaking News - Few hours ago&lt;/h3&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;privacy-policy-for-the-breaking-news-network-mobile-application-and-online-services&#34;&gt;PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE BREAKING NEWS NETWORK MOBILE APPLICATION AND ONLINE SERVICES&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This privacy policy governs your use of the software application BREAKING NEWS NETWORK (BNN) (“Application”) for mobile devices and webpages that were created by BREAKING NEWS NETWORK, INC.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-information-does-the-application-obtain-and-how-is-it-used&#34;&gt;What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-user-provided-information&#34;&gt;1) User Provided Information&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We obtain the following information which you provide when you register the Application.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When you register with us, you generally provide (a) your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, age, employer information, user name, password and other registration information; (b) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us; (c) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (d) credit card information for purchase and use of the Application, and; (e) information you enter into our system when using the Application, such as contact information, and any other information we may request to confirm or verify your identity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;These terms and conditions create a contract between you and Breaking News Network, Inc. (“BNN”) (the “Agreement”). Please read the Agreement carefully. To confirm your understanding and acceptance of the Agreement, click “Agree.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;introduction-to-our-services&#34;&gt;Introduction To Our Services&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This Agreement governs your use of BNN’s services (“Services”), through which you can buy, get, license, rent or subscribe to media, apps (“Apps”), and other in-app services (“Content”). To use our Services, you need compatible hardware, software (latest version recommended and sometimes required) and Internet access (fees may apply). Our Services’ performance may be affected by these factors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
